[
    {
      "_id": "1",
     
      "Question": "Where are you from?",
      "Answer": "  cóng nǎ lǐ lái?",
      "Answer2": " Nǐ cóng lǐ lái?",
      "Answer3": " Nǐ cóng nǎ lǐ ",
      "Ri8_Answer": " Nǐ cóng nǎ lǐ lái?"
    },
    {
      "_id": "2",
      
      "Question": "I come from China",
      "Answer": "Wǒ  zì [Běi jīng]",
      "Answer2": "Wǒ lái  [Běi jīng]",
      "Answer3": "Wǒ lái zì",
      "Ri8_Answer": "Wǒ lái zì [Běi jīng]"
    },
    {
      "_id": "3",
      
      "Question": "I am from Shanghai",
      "Answer": "  [Shàng hǎi] lái",
      "Answer2": " Wǒ cóng  lái",
      "Answer3": " Wǒ cóng [Shàng hǎi] ",
      "Ri8_Answer": " Wǒ cóng [Shàng hǎi] lái"
    },
    {
      "_id": "4",
      
      "Question": "Do you speak [Chinese]",
      "Answer": "N huì shuō [Zhōng wén] ma",
      "Answer2": "Nǐ hshuō [Zhōng wén] ma",
      "Answer3": "Nǐ huì shuō [Zhōng wén] ",
      "Ri8_Answer": "Nǐ huì shuō [Zhōng wén] ma"
    },
    {
      "_id": "5",
      
      "Question": "I can speak a little bit.",
      "Answer": "Wǒ  shuō yī diǎn",
      "Answer2": "Wǒ huì  yī diǎn",
      "Answer3": "Wǒ huì shuō yī ",
      "Ri8_Answer": "Wǒ huì shuō yī diǎn"
    },
    {
      "_id": "6",
      
      "Question": "I can speak Chinese pretty well",
      "Answer": "  Zhōng wén shuō de bú cuò",
      "Answer2": "Wǒ de  wén shuō de bú cuò",
      "Answer3": "Wǒ de Zhōng wén shuō de bú  ",
      "Ri8_Answer": "Wǒ de Zhōng wén shuō de bú cuò"
    },
    {
      "_id": "7",
      
      "Question": "I can barely speak i",
      "Answer": " bù zěn me huì shuō",
      "Answer2": " Wǒ  zěn me huì shuō",
      "Answer3": "Wǒ bù zěn me huì shuō ouwe ",
      "Ri8_Answer": "Wǒ bù zěn me huì shuō"
    },
    {
      "_id": "8",
      
      "Question": "It’s been [three] months / years / weeks / days.",
      "Answer": " Xué le  [sān] (gè) yuè / nián / zhōu / tiān le",
      "Answer2": "Xué le yǒu [sān] (gè) yuè / nián n` / zhōu / tiān le lt",
      "Answer3": "Xué le yǒu [sān] (gè) yuè / nián / zhōu ",
      "Ri8_Answer": "Xué le yǒu [sān] (gè) yuè / nián / zhōu / tiān le"
    },
    {
      "_id": "9",
      
      "Question": "I just got started.",
      "Answer": " Wǒ gāng  kāi shǐ xué x",
      "Answer2": "  gāng gāng kāi shǐ xué x",
      "Answer3": " Wǒ gāng gāng kāi shǐ xué  ",
      "Ri8_Answer": " Wǒ gāng gāng kāi shǐ xué x"
    },
    {
      "_id": "10",
     
      "Question": "I went to [China] on a trip.",
      "Answer": "  qù [Zhōng guó] lǚ yóu guò",
      "Answer2": "Wǒ  [Zhōng guó] lǚ yóu guò",
      "Answer3": "Wǒ qù [Zhōng guó] lǚ yóu ",
      "Ri8_Answer": "Wǒ qù [Zhōng guó] lǚ yóu guò"
    },
    {
      "_id": "11",
      
      "Question": "I once studied in [the United States] for a while",
      "Answer": " Wǒ  zài [Měi guó] liú guò xué",
      "Answer2": "Wǒ céng  [Měi guó] liú guò xué",
      "Answer3": "Wǒ céng zài [Měi guó] liú  ",
      "Ri8_Answer": "Wǒ céng zài [Měi guó] liú guò xué"
    },
    {
      "_id": "12",
      
      "Question": "I visited there for a while.",
      "Answer": "Wǒ zài nà  dāi guò yī zhèn",
      "Answer2": "Wǒ  nà lǐ dāi guò yī zhèn",
      "Answer3": "Wǒ zài nà lǐ dāi guò yī ",
      "Ri8_Answer": "Wǒ zài nà lǐ dāi guò yī zhèn"
    },
    {
      "_id": "13",
      
      "Question": "How is [China]",
      "Answer": "  [Zhōng guó] zěn  yàng",
      "Answer2": " [Zhōng guó]  me yàng",
      "Answer3": " [Zhōng guó] zěn me  ",
      "Ri8_Answer": " [Zhōng guó] zěn me yàng"
    },
    {
      "_id": "14",
     
      "Question": "Very good.",
      "Answer": "  bié hǎo",
      "Answer2": "Tè bié hǎo  bie`",
      "Answer3": "Tè bié hǎo hoo`",
      "Ri8_Answer": "Tè bié hǎo"
    },
    {
      "_id": "15",
      
      "Question": "Not that great",
      "Answer": " Bù zěn  yàng",
      "Answer2": " Bù  me yàng",
      "Answer3": " Bù zěn me ",
      "Ri8_Answer": " Bù zěn me yàng"
    },
    {
      "_id": "16",
      
      "Question": "I don’t enjoy [Chinese] food all that much.",
      "Answer": "  Wǒ  shì hěn xǐ huān [Zhōng guó] cài.",
      "Answer2": " Wǒ bú shì  xǐ huān [Zhōng guó] cài.",
      "Answer3": " Wǒ bú shì hěn huān [Zhōng guó] cài.",
      "Ri8_Answer": " Wǒ bú shì hěn xǐ huān [Zhōng guó] cài."
    },
    {
      "_id": "17",
     
      "Question": "What are you doing?",
      "Answer": " Nǐ zài gàn ma ne ne?",
      "Answer2": "Nǐ  gàn ma ne?",
      "Answer3": "Nǐ zài gàn  ne? ",
      "Ri8_Answer": "Nǐ zài gàn ma ne?"
    },
    {
      "_id": "18",
      
      "Question": "What are you busy with?",
      "Answer": " Nǐ  máng xiē shén me ne?",
      "Answer2": "Nǐ zài  xiē shén me ne?",
      "Answer3": "Nǐ zài máng xiē shén me ? ",
      "Ri8_Answer": "Nǐ zài máng xiē shén me ne?"
    },
    {
      "_id": "19",
      
      "Question": "What’s wrong?",
      "Answer": " shén me bú duì ma?",
      "Answer2": "Yǒu  me bú duì ma?",
      "Answer3": "Yǒu shén me bú duì ?",
      "Ri8_Answer": "Yǒu shén me bú duì ma?"
    },
    {
      "_id": "20",
      
      "Question": "I am not in a good mood.",
      "Answer": " Wǒ  qíng bú tài hǎo",
      "Answer2": "Wǒ  qíng bú tài hǎo",
      "Answer3": "Wǒ xīn qíng bú tài  ",
      "Ri8_Answer": "Wǒ xīn qíng bú tài hǎo"
    }
  ]